TextMe, Incorporated Privacy Policy
===================================

Last Updated on October 13, 2021
--------------------------------

IMPORTANT: BY USING THIS APPLICATION AND/OR OUR PRODUCTS AND SERVICES, INCLUDING THOSE OF OUR AFFILIATES AND SUBSIDIARIES (collectively “TextMe”), YOU SIGNIFY YOUR AGREEMENT TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS APPLICATION OR OUR PRODUCTS AND SERVICES, INCLUDING OUR WEBSITE AND WEB APPLICATIONS. THIS PRIVACY POLICY IS PART OF OUR TERMS AND CONDITIONS WHICH CAN BE ACCESSED ON OUR WEBSITE AND ARE INCORPORATED HEREIN BY REFERENCE, which can be viewed at: [Terms & Conditions](http://api.textme-app.com/api/support/terms-conditions/android/)
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

FOR CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS ONLY [CCPA NOTICE](#CCPA Notice)
---------------------------------------------------------

**1\. Privacy Rights**

TextMe, Incorporated (“Us” or “We” or “Our”) is committed to respecting the privacy rights of its users, customers, visitors, and users of its mobile applications and website, as well as its related services (thereafter “Products and Services”). We created this Privacy Policy to inform you and provide necessary disclosures regarding our collection, use and sharing of information when you use Our Products and Services. We collect, use and share some of your information, as described below, to provide Our Products and Services and to measure and improve them over time. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact Us at: [contactprivacy@go-text.me](mailto: contactprivacy@go-text.me)

**PLEASE SEE TEXTME’S TERMS AND CONDITIONS TO WHICH YOU ARE BOUND IF YOU USE, SUBSCRIBE TO, OR PURCHASE TEXTME’S PRODUCTS OR SERVICES: [Terms & Conditions](http://api.textme-app.com/api/support/terms-conditions/android/)**  

**2\. Not Intended For Use By Children**

Our Products and Services are not directed at children who are under thirteen (13) years of age and We do not knowingly collect personal or other information from children. If you are younger than thirteen (13) years of age, you should not use Our Products and Services and if you are between the ages of thirteen and eighteen you must have parental consent and you should not provide any personal identifiable information while using Our Products and Services without said parental consent. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact Us at [contactprivacy@go-text.me](mailto: contactprivacy@go-text.me).

**3\. Information, Collected, Used and Shared by TextMe, Incorporated**

To provide you with Our Products and Services, we must collect and process information about you. When using Our Products and Services, you consent to the collection, storage, processing, sharing, transfer, manipulation, and disclosure of this information as described in this Privacy Policy.

Regardless of what country you reside in or provide information to Us from, you authorize TextMe to use your information as described herein in the United States and all other countries where TextMe operates or is available.

TextMe retains your information in accordance with legitimate business purposes for processing the information. Thereafter the data is removed, archived for restricted legitimate interests, or anonymized. Non-identifying information may be kept without time and use limitations.

Notice of Collection

What information is collected and how?

* Identifying information, identifiers

* You provide us with identifying information, including your real name, email address, account name, and age bracket. You may also provide us with your gender.
* We associate the identifying information you provide Us with identifying information We collect about you including the account number we assign to your account, the internet protocol (IP) address you use to access our Products and Services, the telephone number We assign to your account, the advertising identifier and device identifier associated with the device you use to access Our Products and Services.

* Commercial information

* We maintain a record of your usage of Our Products and Services, including details about when you logged in and what actions you performed in Our Products and Services,
* Such as logs of messages and calls sent and received,
* And including records of what purchases you made, if any.

* Internet or network activity information

* We collect information about how you access our Products and Services electronically, including device make and model, device settings, operating system, type of connection, carrier information, applications on your device, browser information.

* Geolocation data

* If you have authorized access to your device’s location services, we collect your location.
* Please note that even if you have not authorized access to your device’s location services, we will be able to infer your location via the IP address used to connect to our Products and Services.

* Phone numbers and contact names may be sent to our backend for processing in order to send messages and place calls.

Why do we collect this information?

* We use identifying information to authenticate you in Our Products and Services; to provide you with, and to improve upon, the Products and Services; to carry out actions as instructed by you via your use of the Products and Services; We may contact you with information about Our Products and Services, or to contact as otherwise necessary, including if there has been a data breach; We may notify you of any changes in Our Products and Services, Terms and Conditions, or Privacy Policy.
* We use commercial information to provide you with, and to improve upon, the Products and Services; to carry out actions as instructed by you via your use of the Products and Services; to measure, analyze, and improve upon Our marketing efforts
* We use internet or network activity information to provide you with, and to improve upon, the Products and Services; to carry out actions as instructed by you via your use of the Products and Services; to measure, analyze, and improve upon Our marketing efforts
* We may use your information to provide you with advertisements, including interest-based or personalized advertisements
* We use geolocation data to provide you with, and to improve upon, the Products and Services; to carry out actions as instructed by you via your use of the Products and Services; to measure, analyze, and improve upon Our marketing efforts
* We may use this information to verify or enforce compliance with user agreements and applicable laws, to protect against fraud, to detect and prevent security or technical issues, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the TextMe’s Products and Services, or to protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of TextMe, its subscribers, or the public as required or permitted by law

**4\. Disclosure of Information for Business Purposes**

TextMe does not disclose your Customer Information to third parties except in the limited circumstances herein.

In order to provide you with the Products and Services, we may establish business relationships with third-party companies. We verify that these third-party companies utilize privacy and security practices consistent with Ours.

With your consent, we disclose information to Our advertising providers, in order to provide you with advertisements, including interest-based advertisements. We may disclose identifying information, commercial information, internet or network activity information, and geolocation to advertising providers. Certain advertising providers may also use their own technology to collect information about your use of our Services so that they can provide advertising about products and services tailored to your interests in Our Products and Services, or in other apps and websites. You can find a list of the advertising companies we partner with here: [TextMe Partners](http://textme-www-assets.s3.amazonaws.com/gdpr/textme/consent-2.html)

We disclose information to Our data analytics providers, in order to receive analytical services, which are used to provide, improve upon, and track performance of the Products and Services. We may disclose identifying information, commercial information, internet or network activity information, and geolocation to data analytics providers.

We disclose information to Our marketing providers, in order to communicate with you about our Products and Services. We may disclose identifying information, commercial information, internet or network activity information, and geolocation to marketing providers.

We disclose information to law enforcement agencies in order to respond to law enforcement requests or when legally required to do so. We may disclose identifying information, commercial information, internet or network activity information, and geolocation to law enforcement agencies.

We use third parties to provide hosting and data storage services.

TextMe may disclose or use some of your information if you join a “group” and your prior express consent may be obtained through and conveyed by an intermediary, such as the organizer of a group using TextMe’s Products and Services. To the extent that TextMe sends administrative texts to any group members relating to using and canceling TextMe’s group texting service, they are to be considered normal business communications under applicable law. SEE TEXTME’S TERMS AND CONDITIONS TO WHICH YOU ARE BOUND IF YOU USE, SUBSCRIBE TO, OR PURCHASE TEXTME’S PRODUCTS OR SERVICES.

In the event of a sale, merger, liquidation, dissolution, reorganization, assignment, bankruptcy or any transfer of assets, IP rights, or any marketable right owned by TextMe, your information may be sold or transferred as part of that transaction.

We may use third parties to provide hosting, data storage, and direct marketing services. We may lease, rent, sell or share this information with any third parties to the extent legally possible.

TextMe may provide links and/or connections to third-party applications, websites or services from within Our Products and Services. We may not have access to, or control over, information collected by these third parties. Such third parties will handle, store, retain and access such user information in accordance with the terms and conditions of their agreements with you, if any, as well as their own privacy policies. You acknowledge that TextMe shall have no liability for sharing of such information to such third parties and TextMe disclaims any and all liability relating thereto as set forth in its Terms and Conditions, which are expressly incorporated herein.

**5\. Advertisement Targeting Limitation and Do Not Track**

You can choose to limit the targeting of the various advertisements displayed in TextMe by turning on the feature called “Limit Ad Tracking” which can be located in the settings of your iOS Device or by changing the setting called "Opt out of interest-based ads" settings in Google Settings of your Android Device.

Please note that by limiting the advertising targeting in this manner, you may still see the same number of ads as before, but they may be less relevant because they will not be based on your interests. By invoking this limiting feature, you will still be permitted to use TextMe’s Products and Services.

TextMe does not honor “Do Not Track” header requests.

To learn more about interest-based advertising, or to opt-out, you can visit the site for the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/), or the [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.youradchoices.com/), or the [Interactive Digital Advertising](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/).

**6\. Cookies and Web Beacons**

We may use cookies (a small text file placed on your device to identify your device and browser when you use our Products & Services). We may also use Web beacons (an electronic file placed on a website that monitors usage). Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can instruct your browser to stop accepting cookies (disable cookies). If you do, some of Our Products and Services may not function properly or may be diminished. Promotions or advertisements viewed through Our Products and Services may contain cookies.

**7\. Modifying or Removal of Your Customer Information**

If you have subscribed to or purchased Our Products and Services and you wish to remove or modify your information, you can contact Us using the contact information provided below, although you should be aware that (a) there will be a technical delay between your request and the effective removal of your User Data from Our database, (b) we may have to retain Customer Information for legal purposes as the case may be; and (c) certain of Our Products and Services require the use of your information and such data is retained by Us and used as described in this Privacy Policy. You can delete your account and uninstall the TextMe application from your device. If you need assistance please contact Us at [contactprivacy@go-text.me](mailto: contactprivacy@go-text.me).

**8\. Security of Customer Information**

TextMe seeks to adopt commercially reasonable security measures consistent with the industry regarding the protection against the loss, misuse or alternation of non-public information that is under Our control. Unfortunately, no security system, or system of transmitting data over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As such, you provide all such information at your own risk. In the event that we are required by law to inform you of a breach to your personal information we may notify you electronically, in writing, or by telephone, if permitted to do so by law.

**9\. Changes to TextMe’s Privacy Policy**

TextMe reserves the right, at Our discretion, to change, update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting such change, update or modification on the TextMe website.

Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon notice, which TextMe may provide by any means, including, without limitation, posting on the TextMe website, notifications within TextMe applications, or electronic mail.

Your continued use of the TextMe website and/or any TextMe products and services following the posting of changes will mean you accept those changes. Use of information that We gather is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use.

**10\. For users located in California**

Please see the CCPA Supplement [CCPA NOTICE](#CCPA Notice)

**11\. For users located in the EEA, UK, and Switzerland**

This section only applies to users located in the European Economic Area, United Kingdom, and Switzerland.

You must be at least 16 years of age to use Our Products and Services.

We will request your consent for the processing of personal data for the purpose of providing interest-based advertisements. You can withdraw your consent at anytime by visiting the Settings page in Our Products and Services.

We may also process data as necessary to provide the Products and Services, to comply with legal obligations imposed upon Us, to protect the vital interests of TextMe users, to carry out tasks in the public interest, and other legitimate interests.

Under the General Data Protection Regulation, you have the right to request access, erasure, restriction and portability of your personal data collected by Us.

Your data may be stored in the European Union or the United States. Personal information collected from you, including via the Products and Services, may be transferred to recipients in countries located outside the EEA and the United States which do not provide a similar or adequate level of protection to that provided by countries in the EEA. You hereby expressly consent to the transfer of your personal information to recipients, as described in this Privacy Policy, which are located outside the EEA. We have entered into EU standard contractual clauses (“Model Contracts”) for intra-group transfers of personal information to affiliates.

You can reach our Privacy Officer at [contactprivacy@go-text.me](mailto: contactprivacy@go-text.me).

We can be contacted concerning this Privacy Policy by email at [contactprivacy@go-text.me](mailto: contactprivacy@go-text.me). Please note that this email address should only be used for privacy-related matters and is not a general support contact.

Privacy Policy Supplement Applicable to Residents of California and to which the California Consumer Privacy Act Currently Applies (“CCPA Supplement”)
======================================================================================================================================================

Effective Date: January 1, 2020
-------------------------------

Last Updated on June 11, 2020
-----------------------------

**CCPA Supplement Scope**

The California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) was recently enacted into law and provides California residents with certain rights. This CCPA Supplement details those rights and provides California residents to which the CCPA presently applies with information related to the CCPA and supplements Our Privacy Policy available here Privacy Policy. In the event of any inconsistencies between the provision detailed in this CCPA Supplement and Our Privacy Policy, the provisions of this CCPA Supplement shall prevail and supersede any inconsistencies with Our Privacy Policy as applied to you provided that you are: (i) a resident of California; and (ii) the CCPA is presently applicable to you. Capitalized terms not defined herein shall have the meaning provided for in Our Privacy Policy or [Terms & Conditions](http://api.textme-app.com/api/support/terms-conditions/android/).

For parties to whom this CCPA Supplement applies and have disabilities that require receipt of this notice in an alternative accessible format, please contact Us at [contactprivacy@go-text.me](mailto: contactprivacy@go-text.me) for information as to how to obtain this CCPA Supplement in an alternative format.

**Our Products and Services are Not Intended for Children under the Age of 16 Years Old**

Our Products and Services are not targeted at children under the age of 16 years old. By using Our Products and Services, you represent and warrant that you are at least 16 years old. If We become aware that a customer is under the age of 16 and has provided Us with personal information, We will remove such child’s personal information. A parent or legal guardian who needs to access, change or delete “personal information,” as defined below, regarding their child should contact [contactprivacy@go-text.me](mailto: contactprivacy@go-text.me).

**Definition of “Personal Information”**

As used in this CCPA Supplement, the term “personal information” means information that identifies, relates to, describes, references, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer, household, or device (“personal information”).

“Personal information” does not include:

* De-identified or aggregated consumer information,
* Publicly available information from government records,
* Information excluded from CCPA’s scope including, but not limited to, personal information covered by sector-specific privacy laws like the Fair Credit Reporting Act, the Graham-Leach-Bliley Act, the California Financial Information Privacy Act, and the Driver’s Privacy Protection Act of 1994, and
* Health or medical information covered by the Health Insurance Portability Accountability Act, the California Confidentiality of Medical Information Act or clinical trial data.

**TextMe does not sell personal information.**

**Our Products and Services May Collect the Following Categories of Personal Information from Consumers in the Past Twelve Months**

| Categories of Personal Information That We Collect | Categories of Sources | Business Purpose of Collection | Categories of Third Parties That Receive Data |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| A. Identifiers - A real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, or other similar identifiers. | From Our consumers<br><br>From internet service providers | To provide You with Our Products and Services<br><br>To contact You | Our service providers<br><br>Third parties to whom you allow us to share your information |
| B. Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records statute (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e)) - A name, signature, Social Security number, physical characteristics or description, address, telephone number, passport number, driver’s license or state identification card number, insurance policy number, education, employment, employment history, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information, medical information, or health insurance information. Some personal information included in this category may overlap with other categories. | From Our consumers<br><br>From our payment processors (at the point of collection) | If You make a purchase from Our Products and Services, we may use the financial information You provide to process Your payment | Our service providers<br><br>Our payment processors (who may collect information directly from you, or through us, or who may receive information from us about appropriate charges) |
| C. Protected classification characteristics under California or federal law - Age (40 years or older), race, color, ancestry, national origin, citizenship, religion or creed, marital status, medical condition, physical or mental disability, sex (including gender, gender identity, gender expression, pregnancy or childbirth and related medical conditions), sexual orientation, veteran or military status, genetic information (including familial genetic information). | From Our consumers | To provide You with Our Products and Services | Our service providers<br><br>Third parties to whom you allow us to share your information |
| D. Commercial information - Records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies. | From Our consumers | To provide You with Our Products and Services<br><br>To measure, analyze, and improve upon Our marketing efforts | Our service providers |
| E. Biometric information - Genetic, physiological, behavioral, and biological characteristics, or activity patterns used to extract a template or other identifier or identifying information, such as, fingerprints, faceprints, and voiceprints, iris or retina scans, keystroke, gait, or other physical patterns, and sleep, health, or exercise data. | From Our consumers | Our consumers may provide us with a profile picture or leave a voice message which will be used by Us to deliver the Products & Services | Our service providers |
| F. Internet or other similar network activity - Browsing history, search history, information on a consumer’s interaction with a website, application, or advertisement. | From Our consumers<br><br>From internet service providers | To provide You with Our Products and Services<br><br>To measure, analyze, and improve upon Our marketing efforts | Our service providers |
| G. Geolocation data - Physical location or movements. | From Our Consumers | To provide You with Our Products and Services<br><br>To measure, analyze, and improve upon Our marketing efforts | Our service providers<br><br>Third parties to whom you allow us to share your information |
| H. Sensory data - Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information | Not collected | Not collected | Not collected |
| I. Professional or employment-related information - Current or past job history or performance evaluations | Not collected | Not collected | Not collected |
| J. Non-public education information (per the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (20 U.S.C. Section 1232g, 34 C.F.R. Part 99)) - Education records directly related to a student maintained by an educational institution or party acting on its behalf, such as grades, transcripts, class lists, student schedules, student identification codes, student financial information, or student disciplinary records. | Not collected | Not collected | Not collected |
| K. Inferences drawn from other personal information - Profile reflecting a person’s preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes. | Based upon information collected from our consumers | To provide You with Our Products and Services<br><br>To measure, analyze, and improve upon Our marketing efforts | Our service providers |

**How We Use Personal Information that We Collect**

We may use or disclose the personal information we collect for one or more of the following purposes:

* To fulfill or meet the reason you provided the information. For example, when you purchase Our Products and Services or when you make an in-app purchase, We will request certain information from you or access information you have provided to Us that is associated with your account. This information is likely to include your name, e-mail address, payment card details, billing address and telephone number. This information will be used to process your transaction and to correspond with you in relation to your order. Additionally, We may also save your information to facilitate new orders Our Products and Services or to process refunds.
* To provide, support, personalize and develop Our Products and Services.
* To create, maintain, customize, and secure your account with Us.
* To process your requests, purchases, transactions, and payments and prevent transactional fraud.
* To contact you to inquire whether you want to provide a review of Our Products and Services purchased or to provide other feedback regarding your use of Our Products and Services.
* To engage in marketing communications as well as informational communications with you provided that you opt-in to receive such communications from Us, via email, text message, or as otherwise possible in Our Products and Services.
* To provide you with advertisements, including interest-based or personalized advertisements.
* To enforce contractual commitments that you may enter into with Us including, but not limited to, collection actions.
* To provide you with support and to respond to your inquiries, including to investigate and address your concerns and monitor and improve Our responses.
* To help maintain the safety, security, and integrity of Our Products and Services and systems that support such including databases and other technology assets, and business.
* For testing, research, analysis, and product development, including to develop and improve Our Products and Services.
* To help evaluate the effectiveness of Our marketing and informational communications with you.
* To respond to law enforcement requests and as required by applicable law, court order, or governmental regulations.
* To establish or exercise Our rights, to defend against a legal claim, to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding possible illegal activities, suspected fraud, safety of person or property, or a violation of our policies, or to comply with your request for the shipment of products to or the provision of services by a third party intermediary.
* Some of our websites or applications may provide the opportunity to post comments, or reviews, in a public forum. If you decide to submit information on these pages, that information may be publicly available.
* We may share your information with service providers. Among other things service providers may help us to administer our website, conduct surveys, provide technical support, process payments, and assist in the fulfillment of orders.
* As We have described when collecting your personal information, in Our Privacy Policy, in this CCPA Supplement, or as otherwise set forth in the CCPA.
* In order to evaluate or to conduct the event of a sale, merger, divestiture, liquidation, dissolution, restructuring, reorganization, assignment, bankruptcy or other sale or transfer of some or all of Our any transfer of assets, IP rights, or any marketable right owned by Us, whether as a going concern or as part of a bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by Us or associated with Our Products and Services is among the assets transferred, your personal information may be disclosed, shared, sold or transferred as part of that transaction.
* To provide you with information related to the Products and Services you may have purchased or that may be of interest to you based on your order history or other information you have provided to Us.
* Other Disclosures with Your Consent. We may ask if you would like us to share your information with other unaffiliated third parties who are not described elsewhere in this policy.

We will not collect additional categories of personal information or use the personal information We collected for materially different, unrelated, or incompatible purposes without providing you notice.

**Your Rights Under the CCPA**

If you are a California resident and the CCPA is presently applicable to you, the CCPA provides you with certain specific rights regarding your personal information. This section describes your rights under the CCPA and explains how you can exercise those rights.

**Access to Specific Information and Data Portability Rights**

You have the right to request that We disclose certain information to you about Our collection and use of your personal information over the past 12 months. Once We receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request (see Exercising Access, Data Portability, and Deletion Rights), We will disclose to you:

* The categories of personal information We collected about you.
* The categories of sources for the personal information We collected about you.
* Our business or commercial purpose for collecting that information.
* The categories of third parties with whom We share that personal information.
* The specific pieces of personal information We collected about you (also called a data portability request).
* If We sold or disclosed your personal information for a business purpose, two separate lists disclosing: sales, identifying the personal information categories that each category of recipient purchased; and disclosures for a business purpose, identifying the personal information categories that each category of recipient obtained.

We do not provide these access and data portability rights for business-to-business personal information.

**Deletion Request Rights**

You have the right to request that We delete any of your personal information that We collected from you and retained, subject to certain exceptions. Once We receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request (see [Exercising Access, Data Portability, and Deletion Rights](#Exercising Rights)), We will delete (and direct Our service providers to delete) your personal information from Our records, unless an exception applies.

We may deny your deletion request if retaining the information is necessary for Us or Our service provider(s) to:

* Complete the transaction for which we collected the personal information, provide a good or service that you requested, take actions reasonably anticipated within the context of Our ongoing business relationship with you, or otherwise perform Our contract with you.
* Detect security incidents, protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, or prosecute those responsible for such activities.
* Debug products to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality.
* Exercise free speech, ensure the right of another consumer to exercise their free speech rights, or exercise another right provided for by law.
* Comply with the California Electronic Communications Privacy Act (Cal. Penal Code § 1546 seq.).
* Engage in public or peer-reviewed scientific, historical, or statistical research in the public interest that adheres to all other applicable ethics and privacy laws, when the information’s deletion may likely render impossible or seriously impair the research’s achievement, if you previously provided informed consent.
* Enable solely internal uses that are reasonably aligned with consumer expectations based on your relationship with Us.
* Comply with a legal obligation.
* Make other internal and lawful uses of that information that are compatible with the context in which you provided it.

**Exercising Access, Data Portability, and Deletion Rights**

To exercise the access, data portability, and deletion rights described above, please submit a verifiable consumer request to Us by Submitting a request to Us by visiting the Privacy Center in the Me page of the App (please update to the latest App version).

Only you, or someone legally authorized to act on your behalf, may make a verifiable consumer request related to your personal information. You may also make a verifiable consumer request on behalf of your minor child. You may use an authorized agent to submit a request. To designate an agent for these purposes:

* You must provide us with a copy of a written and signed permission given to your authorized agent; and
* ou must verify your own identity directly with us.

You may only make a verifiable consumer request for access or data portability twice within a 12-month period. The verifiable consumer request must provide sufficient information that allows Us to reasonably verify you are the person about whom we collected personal information or an authorized representative, which may include verifying the email address you used when establishing an account, and by logging into your account and making the request through the app.

We cannot respond to your request or provide you with personal information if we cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm the personal information relates to you.

We will only use personal information provided in a verifiable consumer request to verify the requestor’s identity or authority to make the request.

**Response Timing and Format**

We endeavor to respond to a verifiable consumer request within forty-five (45) days of its receipt. If we require more time (up to 90 days), we will inform you of the reason and extension period in writing.

We will deliver Our written response to the email address You used to setup Your account.

Any disclosures we provide will only cover the 12-month period preceding the verifiable consumer request’s receipt. The response we provide will also explain the reasons we cannot comply with a request, if applicable. For data portability requests, we will select a format to provide your personal information that is readily useable and should allow you to transmit the information from one entity to another entity without hindrance.

We do not charge a fee to process or respond to your verifiable consumer request unless it is excessive, repetitive, or manifestly unfounded. If we determine that the request warrants a fee, we will tell you why we made that decision and provide you with a cost estimate before completing your request.

**Non-Discrimination**

We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your CCPA rights. Unless permitted by the CCPA, we will not:

* Deny you goods or services.
* Charge you different prices or rates for goods or services, including through granting discounts or other benefits, or imposing penalties.
* Provide you a different level or quality of goods or services.
* Suggest that you may receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.

**Other California Privacy Rights**

California’s “Shine the Light” law (Civil Code Section § 1798.83) permits users of Our Products and Services that are California residents to request certain information regarding Our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. We do not currently share personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

**Changes to Our Privacy Notice**

We reserve the right to amend this privacy Notice at Our discretion and at any time. When we make changes to this privacy Notice, we will post the updated Notice on the websites associated with Our Products and Services and update the Notice’s effective date. Your continued use of Our Products and Services following the posting of changes constitutes your acceptance of such changes.

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions or comments about this Notice, the ways in which We collect and use your information described above, your choices and rights regarding such use, or wish to exercise your rights under California law, please do not hesitate to contact Us at: [contactprivacy@go-text.me](mailto: contactprivacy@go-text.me) Please note that this email address should only be used for privacy-related matters and is not a general support contact.
